The young master of the Shangguan family
has the exact symptoms
Senior Medical Maniac taught me about.
He is poisoned by Qilixiang.
Fortunately,
I know how to make the antidote.
But we are missing a key ingredient here.
Where can I find the blood
of a divine beast?
That's simple.
You just need to take a drop
of your own blood.
I am not a divine beast.
Trust me.
You'll know once you try.
The young master is awake!
My blood actually worked.
Who exactly am I?
Master Shangguan actually
gave me a new residence directly.
I have my own home now.
But
I am the only one at home.
This is...
Meet me outside the city gate
at Hai hour tonight.
Is anyone there?
Who wrote this note?
Orchids.
Lady Feng Qingwu.
Among the people I know,
only you have the scent of orchids.
Come out.
You are quite smart.
It saves me from beating around the bush.
There is nothing else.
I called you here
just to kill you.
I have already left Mister.
Why do you still hate me so much?
Who knows what kind of potion
you gave the Chief?
After you left, he went crazy
and had everyone look for you everywhere.
M-Mister...
Die!
Chief!
I found her on your orders,
but she tried to kill me to silence me.
I was just fighting back.
She is twisting the truth.
But Mister will definitely choose
to believe his fiancée, right?
Ah!
Come back with me.
What?
Say it again.
I want you to come back with me.
He already consummated his relationship
with Feng Qingwu,
yet he still asks me to go back with him?
Young Master Yan.
I won't go back with you.
We are just strangers after all.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Mister!
Chief!
Madam, you are finally back.
The Chief has been looking for you everywhere
without eating or drinking these days.
Stop lying to me.
I already know.
He and Feng Qingwu have already
consummated their relationship.
Feng Qingwu is best at illusions.
You must have been deceived by her.
Other than you,
the Chief has never fallen for any woman
in a thousand years.
So I misunderstood Mister?
He was so anxious after I left.
Does he really like me?
This girl said she was going
to brew medicine,
but ended up falling asleep here.
Mister, why do you have to have a fiancée?
So annoying.
Silly girl.
I don't have any marriage contract
with Feng Qingwu.
Not now,
and not ever.
Girl,
let go.
No, I want you to sleep with me.